Guide to the Pennsylvania Economy League Records, 1925-1985 AIS.1978.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Municipal Governments, 1929-1975; II.
  - Shenango Valley, "An Animal Control Program Proposal for the Shenango Valley Part II- Administration", August, 1966
  - Shenago Valley, "A Report on the Public Transportation Problem", November, 1958
  - South Greensburg, "Review of Financial Operations South Greensburgh Borough 1953-1959", October, 1959
  - South Greensburg, "Planning for a Swimming Pool", October, 1959
  - South Union, "Economic Justification for a Sewage System", May, 1966
  - Strasburg, "A Review of the Borough of Strasburg Water System", April, 1956
  - Stroudsburg, "A Study Regarding Potentials of Consolidation", October, 1957
  - Sutersville, "A Suggested Accounting System", October, 1958
  - Sutersville, "A Review of Financial Operations 1951-1958", October, 1958
  - Tarentum, "A Fiscal Analysis", January, 1963
  - Tarentum, "A Preliminary Analysis of Parking Conditions", August, 1951
  - Tarentum, "Review of the Fiscal Analysis", July, 1964
  - Tarentum, "Financial Review and Rate Comparison Borough of Tarentum Water Department", January, 1968
  - Titusville, "Report on Existing Methods for the Collection and Disposal of Garbage and Other Refuse Together with Analysis of Rare Structors", July, 1951
  - Titusville, "A Report on Commercial Refuse Collection", August, 1961
  - Turtle Creek, "A Study of Municipal Finance", March, 1954
  - Turtle Creek, "A Review of Turtle Creek's Liability and Property Insurance Program with Specifications for a Special Multiperil Policy", March, 1975
  - Turtle Creek, "A Review of Turtle Creek's Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Insurance Coverage with Specifications", January, 1975
  - Turtle Creek, "Turtle Creek Financial Program and Projections", July, 1966
  - Uniontown, "Analysis of Existing Methods for the Collection and Disposal for Garbage, Ashes, and Other Refuse and Suggestions to Improve the Service", March, 1950
  - Uniontown, "The Earned Income Tax: an Analysis of Revenue Trends and Collection Procedures for the City of Uniontown", November, 1976
  - Uniontown, "Memorandum on the 1949 Budget of the City of Uniontown as of October 1, 1949 with Projections to End of Year", November, 1949
  - Uniontown, "City of Uniontown and the Police Department 1968", December, 1968
  - Uniontown, "Financial Analysis of City of Uniontown", January, 1945
  - Uniontown, "Fiscal and Background Data City of Uniontown", November, 1969
  - Uniontown, "A Proposed Accounting System for the City of Uniontown- Volume I Text", September, 1948
  - Uniontown, "A Proposed Accounting System for the Uniontown – Volume II Exhibits", September, 1948
  - Uniontown, "Financial Analysis of City of Uniontown 1944-1945 and the 1946 Budget", July, 1946
  - Upper Marion, "The Anatomy of Township Growth", May, 1965
  - Upper Marion, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection Township of Upper St. Clair 1959-1969", July, 1964
  - Vandergrift, "Five Year Financial Analysis and Budget Review", May, 1964
  - Vandergrift, "A Survey of Parking Conditions in Vandergrift Borough", February, 1953
  - Vandergrift, "A Review of the Proposal for an Off-Street Parking Facility", October, 1965 (Box 24)
  - Vandergrift, "A Study of Financial Trends 1952-1968 Borough of Vandergrift", November, 1962
  - Washington City, "A Look at the Feasibility Report for the Proposed Swimming Pool", March, 1965
  - Washington City, "Fiscal Analysis Past, Present, and Future (1968-1977)", April, 1973
  - Washington City, "Comparative Insurance Protection Costs of Selected Third-Class Cities", July, 1966
  - Washington City, "A Review of the Fire Protection Contracts", September, 1961
  - Washington City, "A Fiscal Analysis and Projection for the City of Washington 1959-1970", December, 1965
  - Washington City, "The Impact of Washington City's Financial Structure of Financing the City's Share of the Costs of the Central City Redevelopment Project", May, 1962
  - Washington City, "Critical Decision in the Future: An Analysis of Major Administrative Policy Problems Facing the City of Washington", November, 1976
  - Washington City, "Procedures to Follow to Forma Sanitary Authority", May, 1948
  - Washington City, "Report on Revenue Accounting System", January, 1946
  - Washington City, "Report on an Accounting System for the City of Washington", May, 1943
  - Washington City, "Report on the Financial Affairs and Revenue Accounting", April, 1945
  - Washington City, "Confidential Report on a Preliminary Study of the City of Washington, PA. As Related to the 1943 Budget", January, 1943
  - Washington City, "Confidential Report on the City of Washington 1944 Budget", December, 1943
  - Washington City, "A Proposed Position Classification Plan", May, 1968
  - Washington City, "City of Washington Budget Analysis – 1953", October, 1952
  - Washington City, "A Report on Parking Needs in the City of Washington with Recommendations", June, 1958
  - Washington City, "Job Classification Study", June, 1956
  - Waynesburg, "The Fiscal Profile of Waynesburg 1969-1978", July, 1974
  - Waynesburg, "Financial Review of Waynesburg Borough (1941-1950) and a Capital Improvement Program", May, 1951
  - Waynesburg, "The Advisability of Levying Sewer Rental, Rates, or Changes," October, 1958
  - Waynesburg, "An Analysis for Waynesburg Borough of Current and Projected Traffic Volume at the South Morgan Intersection", December, 1977
  - Waynesburg, "Memorandum Report on Waynesburg's General Fund Finances Jan. 1 1958-Oct. 1 1958", October, 1958
  - Waynesburg, "Memorandum Report on Waynesburg Finances Jan. 1 1959-Oct. 1 1959," October, 1959
  - Waynesburg, "An Analysis of Off Street Parking", June, 1974
  - Waynesburg, "Survey and Report for Accounting System", March, 1955
  - Waynesburg, "A Study of the Parking and Traffic Problem", March, 1956
  - Waynesburg, "Analysis of the Financial Operations 1954 and Ten Months of 1955", November, 1955
  - Waynesburg, "An Analysis of the Waynesburg Borough Budget for 1957", February, 1957
  - Waynesburg, "Merger Study of Waynesburg Borough – Franklin Township", October, 1967
  - Waynesburg, "Municipal Employee Retirement System", December, 1962
  - Weirton, "Position Classification Study", March, 1967
  - Weirton, "Projection of 1960-61 Budget", July, 1960
  - Weirton, "Weirton Sanitary Board Fiscal Study", November, 1963
  - West Chester, "1954 Fiscal Delemma", March, 1954
  - West Homestead, "A Report on the Survey of the Borough of West Homestead", July, 1951
  - West Kittanning, "Current Fiscal Picture of West Kittanning Borough and the Impact of Annexation", April, 1963
  - West Kittanning, "A Financial Analysis", May, 1960
  - West Leechburg, "Memorandum on the Revised Plan of the Proposed West Leechburg Water System", June, 1947
  - West Leechburg, "A Fiscal Review and Forecast and Sewer Project Financing Alternatives", November, 1975
  - West Leechburg, "Report on the Proposed Water System", May, 1947
  - West Middlesex, "Alternative Staffing Patterns and Corresponding Costs for Municipal Police Department July1, 1977 through December 31, 1977", June, 1977
  - West Middlesex, "West Middlesex Union School Study", August, 1960
  - West Newton, "A Brief Financial Review of the Borough of West Newton", February, 1951
  - West Newton, "Financial Problems of A Sewage Disposal System", July, 1964
  - West Newton, "A Proposed Off-Street Parking Lot", July, 1958
  - West Newton, "A Study of Downtown Parking Facilities and Traffic Regulation", March, 1955
  - West View, "Proposed Accounting System", March, 1945
  - West View, "A Review of the 1945 Budget of the Borough of West View with Recommended Revisions", February, 1945
  - West View, "Financial Analysis Borough of West View 1940-1943", February, 1945
  - Wharton, "An Economic Justification for the Big Sandy Watershed Project", October, 1967
  - Wheatland, "Financial Analysis Study the Years 1957-1961 and 1964", November, 1965
  - Wheatland, "Alternatives for Financing a Proposed Municipal Building", October, 1973
  - Wheatland, "A Simplified Accounting System", December, 1960
  - White, "Annexation for White Township Map of Beer Falls Area", May, 1955
  - Whitehall, "Report on the Survey of Earned Income Tax Accounting", July, 1954
  - Whitehall, "Survey an Report for General Accounting System", September, 1954
  - Whitaker, "Borough of Whitaker Accounting System", May, 1956
  - Whitaker, "Borough of Whitaker Budget Estimates – 1956", March, 1956
  - Wilkes-Barre, "Fleet management Survey of the City of Wilkes-Barre", December, 1960
  - Wilkes-Barre, "Report on 1958 Budget of Wilkes-Barre City", December, 1957
  - Wilkes-Barre, "Report on Wilkes-Barre City Tentative Budget 1959", December, 1958
  - Wilkes-Barre, "Report on the High School Plant Program", October, 1950
  - Wilkes-Barre, "A Report on Wilkes-Barre City School Construction Plans", December, 1952
  - Wilkes-Barre, "A Review of Wilkes-Barre City Finances and Report on the Purposed Budget for the Year 1957", December, 1956
  - Wilkes-Barre, "Equalized Secondary Educational Facilities", December, 1950
  - Wilkes-Barre, "Ten Years of Wilkes-Barre City Finances", November, 1952
  - Wilkes-Barre, "Summary of Wilkes-Barre City Fiscal Results 1959 and Proposed Financial Program for 1960", January, 1960
  - Wilkes-Barre, "The Effect of Reassessment", October, 1964
  - Wilkes-Barre, "Administration of the Wilkes-Barre City Residence Tax", March, 1963
  - Wilkinsburg, "Fire Protection in Wilkinsburg", July, 1969
  - Wilkinsburg, "Put Experience on the Line: An Administrative Study of the Wilkinsburg Police Department", October, 1975
  - Wilmerding, "Preliminary Fiscal Analysis of the Borough of Wilmerding 1958-1962", May, 1963
  - Youngstown, "Planning and Financing a Sewage Disposal System", October, 1961
- Counties, 1937-1987; III.
  The County Government series consists of studies and reports produced for various county government agencies and primarily focuses on budgets, real estate assessment, housing, transportation, staffing levels, construction projects, and a wide range of other issues.
  - Allegheny, "An ACTION Program from Meeting the Housing Problems of Allegheny County", February, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Allegheny, "Administrative and Management Study of the Office of Sheriff of Allegheny County Part I: Revising the Sheriff's Role in the Selection and Notification of Jurors", August, 1970
  - Allegheny, "Administrative and Management Study of the Office of Sheriff of Allegheny County Part II: Preparation of Returns Service", August, 1970
  - Allegheny, "An Administrative Study of the Family Division", January, 1975
  - Allegheny, "Allegheny County Housing Authority Personnel Classification and pay Plan", May, 1975
  - Allegheny, "Allegheny County Housing Authority Personnel Classification and pay Plan", July, 1969
  - Allegheny, "Analysis of the 1945 Budget Estimates Allegheny County", February, 1945
  - Allegheny, "Analysis of the 1946 Budget Allegheny County", March, 1946
  - Allegheny, "Analysis of the 1947 Budget of Allegheny County", March, 1947
  - Allegheny, "An Analysis of Factors Influencing the Demand for Present and Future Hangar Facilities at Allegheny County Airport", March, 1961
  - Allegheny, "An Analysis of Grants Management in Allegheny County", December, 1982
  - Allegheny, "An Analysis of Minor Judiciary Costs and Fees Paid by Allegheny County", April, 1953
  - Allegheny, "Analysis of the Non-Mental Patients at the Allegheny County Home and Hospital", July, 1941
  - Allegheny, "Architectural Report for Board of County Commissioners County of Allegheny Commonwealth of Pennsylvania: Public Buildings Additions and Space Analysis Department of Property and Supplies Allegheny County, Pennsylvania", August, 1959
  - Allegheny, "The Burden on Real Estate in Allegheny County for the Support of Public Education by Districts and by Class of Districts", July, 1952
  - Allegheny, "Comments on the Administration of Allegheny County Parks as Related to the 1941 Budget Requests", January, 1941
  - Allegheny, "Comments on the 1940 Budget of the County of Allegheny", January, 1940
  - Allegheny, "Comments on the 1941 Budget of the County of Allegheny", February, 1941
  - Allegheny, "Comments on the 1942 Budget of the County of Allegheny", February, 1942
  - Allegheny, "Comments on the 1943 Budget of the County of Allegheny", February, 1943
  - Allegheny, "Comments on the 1944 Budget of the County of Allegheny", February, 1944
  - Allegheny, "Comments on the 1952 Budget Allegheny Count", February, 1952
  - Allegheny, "Compensation of Top Management Positions in 14 County and City-County Governments for 1968", June, 1968
  - Allegheny, "Compilation of Pertinent Information from Lease Agreements in Effect at Selected Airport on May 1, 1961", May, 1961
  - Allegheny, "Conclusions and Recommendations Regarding Military Operations at the Greater Pittsburgh Airport", March, 1956
  - Allegheny, "Cost Comparison of Alternative Proposal Submitted to Allegheny County for the MH/MR Data Center", November, 1983
  - Allegheny, "County Budget Study: Recorder of Deeds' Office", November, 1937
  - Allegheny, "County Road Transfer Study", July, 1958
  - Allegheny, "County Road Transfer Study: Revised Edition", December, 1959
  - Allegheny, "Court Cost Allocation Manual for Preparation", April, 1987
  - Allegheny, "Court Cost Allocation Plan 1985", February, 1987
  - Allegheny, "The Court Cost Collection System and Procedures of the Clerk of Courts, Allegheny County: Analysis and Recommendations", November, 1986
  - Allegheny, "Data and Suggestions to Guide Negotiations on 1954-1962 Agreements with the Tenants of Greater Pittsburgh Airport", November, 1956
  - Allegheny, "The Delaware Expressway: Free or Toll?", August, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Department of Property and Supply Motor Vehicle Repair Facilities", January, 1958
  - Allegheny, "Department of Property and Supplies Allegheny County's Automotive Fleet", May, 1958
  - Allegheny, "Direct Exhibits: The Pittsburgh Parties", December, 1986
  - Allegheny, "An Examination of the Feasibility of Expanding the Capabilities of Allegheny County's Print Shop", December, 1982
  - Allegheny, "Exhibits Community Fiscal Study", 1961
  - Allegheny, "Factsheet on Allegheny County Compilation of Assessments, Tax, Sources, Legal Rate Limits and Levies", 1971 (Box 26)
  - Allegheny, "Final Report: Planning Committee on Long Term Care for the Elderly", June, 1979
  - Allegheny, "Financing the Civic Auditorium", January, 1956
  - Allegheny, "Financing of County Capital Improvements", March, 1974
  - Allegheny, "Financing of Major Capital Improvement: County of Allegheny and Allegheny County Institution District", June, 1972
  - Allegheny, "A Financial Program for Allegheny County", 1940
  - Allegheny, "Fiscal Trends Allegheny County and Institution District 1968-1974", December, 1975
  - Allegheny, "Formal Long-Range Capital Improvement Programming and Budgeting for the County of Allegheny", July, 1953
  - Allegheny, "Forecast of Major Local Government Finances within the County of Allegheny", 1969
  - Allegheny, "A Forecast of Passenger Volume, Operations, and Finances Greater Pittsburgh Airport 1965-1970-1975", October, 1965
  - Allegheny, "Greater Pittsburgh Airport Advisory Committee's Proposed Capital Improvement Program", December, 1964
  - Allegheny, "Greater Pittsburgh Airport Advisory Committee's Proposed Capital Improvement Program", March, 1965
  - Allegheny, "Greater Pittsburgh Airport Business Survey for June, 1953", September, 1953
  - Allegheny, "Greater Pitt – Gateway to the World", May, 1969
  - Allegheny, "Greater Pitt – Gateway to the World: Appendix", May, 1969
  - Allegheny, "Handbook Containing Questions and Answers Relative to Public Health and the Allegheny County Health Department", September, 1956
  - Allegheny, "Historical Review of the Allegheny County Sanitary Authority", January, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Income Development Recommendations Greater Pittsburgh Airport", February, 1953
  - Allegheny, "Interim Forecast: Traffic at Greater Pittsburgh Airport", November, 1956
  - Allegheny, "Inventory of Public health Services Personnel and Relevant Data", June, 1956
  - Allegheny, "Issues Surrounding the Planning of Capital Improvements to Allegheny County Hospitals", April, 1978
  - Allegheny, "John J. Kane Hospital Federal and State Reimbursements Public vs. Private Nonprofit Facility", May, 1977
  - Allegheny, "Long-Range Capital Improvement Program Greater Pittsburgh Airport, Sec I and II", November, 1953
  - Allegheny, "Long-Range Capital Improvement Program Greater Pittsburgh Airport, Sec III, IV and V", January, 1954
  - Allegheny, "Management Control Report I: Summary Report February, 1969"
  - Allegheny, "Master Plan for Future Operations at the Allegheny County Municipal Airport", February, 1953
  - Allegheny, "Mining and Physiography", November, 1968
  - Allegheny, "A New Administration Mechanism for Allegheny County", October, 1972
  - Allegheny, "The New Local Debt Limitation Legislation and Its Effects on Allegheny County", July, 1972
  - Allegheny, "Organizing for Economic Development in Allegheny County", January, 1977
  - Allegheny, "Organization and Initial Operation of the New Allegheny County Institution District Hospital", February, 1957
  - Allegheny, "Pay and Fringe Benefit Policies Applicable to Uniform Police Forces of Selected Agencies", April, 1972 (Box 27)
  - Allegheny, "The Penal System of Allegheny County", February, 1958
  - Allegheny, "A Personnel and Administrative Study for the Allegheny County Court of Common Pleas Part I", January, 1970
  - Allegheny, "A Personnel and Administrative Study for the Allegany County Court of Common Pleas, Part II", January, 1970
  - Allegheny, "Photocopying Equipment and Costs Allegheny County", June, 1980
  - Allegheny, "A Plan to Reorganize the United Fund of Allegheny County", December, 1973
  - Allegheny, "Probable Locations of Sanitary Fills in Allegheny County, Pennsylvania", December, 1952
  - Allegheny, "The Problem of Records Management in Allegheny County", June, 1958
  - Allegheny, "Proposal for the Reorganization of the Department of Registration and Elections County of Allegheny", March, 1969
  - Allegheny, "Proposed Geographical Recording for the Board of Assessment and Revision of Taxes of Allegheny County", May, 1938
  - Allegheny, "A Proposed Refuse Disposal System for Allegheny County", December, 1958
  - Allegheny, "Proposed Reorganization of the Department of Aviation", March, 1970
  - Allegheny, "Proposed Manual of Standard operating Instructions For Implementation of a Management Control System for Allegheny County", April, 1969
  - Allegheny, "A Proposed Personnel Program for Allegheny County and Allegheny County Institutional District: Volume I", August, 1959
  - Allegheny, "A Proposed Personnel Program for Allegheny County and Allegheny County Institutional District: Volume II," (1 of 5), August, 1959
  - Allegheny, "A Proposed Personnel Program for Allegheny County and Allegheny County Institutional District: Volume II," (2 of 5), August, 1959
  - Allegheny, "A Proposed Personnel Program for Allegheny County and Allegheny County Institutional District: Volume II," (3 of 5), August, 1959
  - Allegheny, "A Proposed Personnel Program for Allegheny County and Allegheny County Institutional District: Volume II," (4 of 5), August, 1959
  - Allegheny, "A Proposed Personnel Program for Allegheny County and Allegheny County Institutional District: Volume II," (5 of 5), August, 1959
  - Allegheny, "A Prospectus for Research, Education and Service in the Field of Health", March, 1958
  - Allegheny, "Recommendations for the Division of Property and Services at the Allegheny Home and Hospital between the County and the State", May, 1941
  - Allegheny, "Reevaluation of the United Fund of Allegheny County: Study Prospectus", July, 1973
  - Allegheny, "Refuse Collection Survey Allegheny County", February, 1938
  - Allegheny, "The Refuse Disposal Problem in Allegheny County", January 1959
  - Allegheny, "Reimbursement Allowances for County Employees Using Private Cars For the Execution of County Business", March, 1957
  - Allegheny, "Report on the Allegheny County Debt", June, 1937
  - Allegheny, "Report to the Allegheny County Salary Board on the Board of Viewers", June, 1977
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Fiscal Practices and Problems of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Authorities in Allegheny County", February, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Fiscal Practices and Problems of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Fiscal Inventory Practices and Problems in Allegheny County", February, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Fiscal Practices and Problems of the Metropolitan Study Commission: The Function of Public Welfare as Administered in Allegheny County", March, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Fiscal Practices and Problems of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Tax Collection as Administered In Allegheny County", March, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Fiscal Highways, Streets, and Bridges of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Construction and Maintenance of Streets and Bridges", January, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Fiscal Highways, Streets, and Bridges of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Minor Judiciary Offices as Administered in Allegheny County", October, 1954
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Independent County Officers and Elections of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Independent County Offices as Administered in Allegheny County", December, 1954
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Land Use of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Building Regulations As Administered in Allegheny County", December, 1954
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Land Use of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Planning as Administered in Allegheny County", January, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Land Use of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Public Housing in Allegheny", December, 1954
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Land Use of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Subdivision Regulations as Administered in Allegheny County", December, 1954
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Land Use of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Zoning Regulations as Administered in Allegheny County", December, 1954
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Parks and Recreation of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Public Parks and Recreation as Administered by Allegheny County", February, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Public Health and Welfare of the Metropolitan Study Commission: The Function of Public Welfare as Administered in Allegheny County", January, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Public Health and Welfare of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Minimum Housing Regulations as Administered in Allegheny County", October, 1954
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Public Health and Welfare of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Plumbing Regulations as Administered in Allegheny County", October, 1954
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Transportation and Parking of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Traffic Engineering and parking as Administered in Allegheny County", January, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Transportation and Parking of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Mass Transit in Allegheny County", January, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Water Supply and Sanitation of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Refuse Collection and Disposal in Allegheny County", November, 1955
  - Allegheny, "Report of Committee on Water Supply and Sanitation of the Metropolitan Study Commission: Sanitary Sewage Facilities in Allegheny County", October, 1954